Hierarchy	Title	Description	Project	Releases	Teams	Members	Sprints	Earliest start	Target start	Scheduled start	Due date	Target end	Scheduled end	Story Points	Original Story Points	Parent	Labels	Components	Themes	Issue key	Issue status	Epic/Theme	Progress (%)	Progress completed	Progress remaining
Initative	Enhancing Insight Functionalities	This initiative will contain following features:   * PPT export   * PPT and Excel Export of Collections   * Sharing Favorites and Collections   * Localisation of the Insight UI   * etc.    i.e. improving client user experience.	Market Reporting	"Old Fashioned, Gin & Tonic"	"MR BI Team Team, MR PO/PD Team Team, MR PS Team Team"	"Alexander Firsching, Volko Christ"	"MR PS Team Team: Sprint 4, MR BI Team Team: Sprint 4"			28. August 2018			10. September 2018	18						NEO-1323	Open		0	0	18
Feature	Release Notes in Insight	"The goal of this feature is to provide release notes (features and/or functions information) in the Insight directly. At the moment this infomation is being communicated via CCR Community to the local team, who later are in chanrge of the communication to the clients.          Benefit:    Improve client satisfactioon         Acceptence Criteria:   * show in the insight that there are new features/functions available    * provide a file where the description can be added (the text should be formated properly,e.g. font size.)   * Similar behaviour as it is available for newly loaded elements in the product hierarchy. This means if the user already looked at the new funtions, then this information should not pop-up anymore.     "	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Enhancing Insight Functionalities	RS_RN_yes	"Conditioned Feature Backlog, Product Offering / Product Design"		NEO-1325	Open		0	0	0
Epic	Introduce Notifications to RetailScout	"As a User of RS I want to know if there are new features in the interface, so that I can try them out. "	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Release Notes in Insight		Product Offering / Product Design		NEO-2558	Open		0	0	0
Story	Is getting data from Confluence feasible?	"Since the Release Notes will be released on Confluence, it would be practical to get the information for the Release Notes in Retail Scout directly from there.     This spike should gives us insights into:    * How much effort will we have using the API? [https://developer.atlassian.com/server/confluence/confluence-rest-api-examples/]   * What kind of technical challenges will we have?    * What kind of data validation challenges will we have?    * etc...    If there are severe doubts of whether we should use Confluence, then this Spike should also contain possible better alternatives."	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Introduce Notifications to RetailScout		Product Offering / Product Design		NEO-2559	Open		0	0	0
Feature	Stretch Objective: Improve PPT export - vertical pagination	"At the moment when using an powerpoint export functionality, each exported report will be fitted to a powerpoint slide. In some case when the report is too large for one slide, a pagination (cutting in to several pictures) is required, so the that the information provided by the report can be read easily.    Benefit:    improve customer satisfaction    Acceptence Criteria:   * export report which exceeds (vertically) the acceptable powerpoint slide   * the report should be cut into several images, thereby totals and legend need to be repeated, so that the report's context is not lost.   * in case of grouping - the grouping chould not be split over several slides     "	Market Reporting	"Gin & Tonic, Old Fashioned"												Enhancing Insight Functionalities	RS_RN_yes	"Conditioned Feature Backlog, Product Offering / Product Design"		NEO-1888	Open		0	0	0
Feature	Enable export of the tables (116/101) report	Support powerpoint export for tables.At the momet suported only for charts.    Benefit:   * improve customer satisfaction    Acceptance Criteria:   * Report 101 and 116 can exported to powerpoint	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned	"MR BI Team Team, MR PO/PD Team Team, MR PS Team Team"	"Alexander Firsching, Volko Christ"	"MR PS Team Team: Sprint 4, MR BI Team Team: Sprint 4"			28. August 2018			10. September 2018	18		Enhancing Insight Functionalities	RS_RN_yes	"Conditioned Feature Backlog, Product Offering / Product Design"		NEO-1159	Open		0	0	18
Epic	PPT Export tables first draft		Market Reporting	Old Fashioned	"MR BI Team Team, MR PO/PD Team Team, MR PS Team Team"	"Alexander Firsching, Volko Christ"	"MR PS Team Team: Sprint 4, MR BI Team Team: Sprint 4"			28. August 2018			10. September 2018	18		Enable export of the tables (116/101) report		Product Offering / Product Design		NEO-1209	Open		0	0	18
Story	Integrate Excel Export into Export Service	"     As a software developer I want to separate the Excel Export from the Query Service into an own Export Service, so that the maintainability is easier and there is a clear separation of concerns.    +Background:+    Until now, the Excel Export is integrated into the Query Service. Since there is also the Powerpoint Export, it makes more sense to integrate both into an own Export Service. This enhances maintainability of the code. First setup and building skeleton of the Export Service is included in this User Story. Refactoring is also included in this story. "	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned	MR PS Team Team		MR PS Team Team: Sprint 4			28. August 2018			10. September 2018	13		PPT Export tables first draft		Product Offering / Product Design		NEO-1063	Open		0	0	13
Sub-Task	Integrate new File-Export-Service in the Frontend	Connect to the new file-export service when exporting Excel files.	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Integrate Excel Export into Export Service		Product Offering / Product Design		NEO-1195	Open		0	0	0
Sub-Task	Set up Platinum Cloud Server for Export Service	Set up a Platinum Cloud Server for the FileExportService    Enable Deployment     Add Monitoring to the Server	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Integrate Excel Export into Export Service	DevOps	Product Offering / Product Design		NEO-1391	Open		0	0	0
Story	Integrate Powerpoint Export into Export Service	"As a software developer I want to separate the Powerpoint Export from the Query Service into an own Export Service, so that the maintainability is easier and there is a clear separation of concerns.    +Background:+    Until now, the Powerpoint Export is integrated into the Query Service. Since there is also the Excel Export, it makes more sense to integrate both into an own Export Service. This enhances maintainability of the code."	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned	MR BI Team Team	"Alexander Firsching, Volko Christ"	MR BI Team Team: Sprint 4			28. August 2018			10. September 2018	5		PPT Export tables first draft		Product Offering / Product Design		NEO-1062	Open		0	0	5
Story	Enable PPT export of tables as one large picture		Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			PPT Export tables first draft		Product Offering / Product Design		NEO-1768	Open		0	0	0
Story	Enable PPT export of tables WYSIWYG	"As a Retailer, I want to export the 116 Report directly into Powerpoint as one large picture, so that can directly work with it.    +Acceptance Criteria:+    * tbd"	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned	MR PO/PD Team Team					14. August 2018			24. September 2018			PPT Export tables first draft		Product Offering / Product Design		NEO-454	Open		0	0	0
Epic	Enable PPT export of tables with pagination		Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Enable export of the tables (116/101) report		Product Offering / Product Design		NEO-1769	Open		0	0	0
Feature	Provide direct access to Collections	List and provide access to the last 10 used collections on Landing Page.    Benefit:    improve client satisfaction by easier access to the colletions.         Acceptance Criteria:   * add separate accordion on LP   * list collections     	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Enhancing Insight Functionalities	RS_RN_yes	"Conditioned Feature Backlog, Product Offering / Product Design"		NEO-1569	Open		0	0	0
Initative	RetailScout scales to 1200 retailers		Market Reporting	"Old Fashioned, Gin & Tonic"						14. August 2018			24. September 2018							NEO-287	In Progress		0	0	0
Feature	Re-use panelmarket figures for all clients in one country	"Example:    for RU PM is being calculated 24 times, although the figures are exactly the same for all retailers in RU.     calculation times for RU:    Retailer + CH-ME:      28min    PM + CH:                  170min    estimated time reduction ca 40%          The goal is to identify identical panelmarket (can it be also done for the CH?) in one country are share the figures for all retailers.         Benefits:   - reduce HW costs, due reduced data volume"	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			RetailScout scales to 1200 retailers	RS_RN_yes	"BI Layer, Conditioned Feature Backlog, Product Offering / Product Design, Product Subscription, Reporting Data Preparation"		NEO-1969	Open		0	0	0
Feature	Reduce time needed to process the data  (FTP->AS)	"Currently the time needed to process data from FTP to AWS can take up to 26 hours:    13 h waiting time in queue    4 h check if new data is available    7 h pre-processing data    At the moment the requirement is to process the data within 4h.         Benefit:    improve customer satisfaction by delievering data in time    Business Value:    5 - high         Acceptance Criteria:   * evaluate the time needed to preprocess the data, come up with the  possible solutions to reduce the time   * Document the solutions, align with architect   * implement the solution"	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			RetailScout scales to 1200 retailers	RS_RN_no	Product Subscription		NEO-2459	Open		0	0	0
Feature	**Scale up RS from 200 to 400 clients (Wave 4)	"Currenty we have rolled out 130 retailers, in the next month we expect set up and rollout of ca. 300 additional retailers.    In order to enable efficient rollout of further clients and improve our cost structure we need:   * set up and configure data marts     - Migrate PS servers in cloud   - provide manual for NCDM   - support of the client rollout         Benefit: enable savings and increase dev efficiency    Acceptance Critearia:   * NL DataMarts required for rollout of the clients has been setup   * PS (preprocessing) instances are migrated to AWS cloude   * NCDM manual is in place   * manual weekly update of the content changes is done     "	Market Reporting	"Gin & Tonic, Old Fashioned"												RetailScout scales to 1200 retailers	RS_RN_no	"BI Layer, Conditioned Feature Backlog, Product Subscription, Reporting Data Preparation"		NEO-833	In Progress		0	0	0
Feature	"Enable additional exclusivity handling ""Agg to TB&Excl"" to rollout furhter countries "	"In order to be able to rollout AU & NZ retailers we need to support ""Agg to TB&Excl."" Exclusivity Handling on Item Level.     Benefit: we will be able to rollout countries like AU & NZ    Enable savings    Acceptance Criteria:    * Items with ""agg to TB&Excl"" handling mode are displayed as a single tag in the All Hitlists   * TB&Excl are excluded from the Top X Calculation and added to Others   * TB&Excl are shown in a separate line in hitlists.   * TB&Excl figures reflect Feature and/or PCL filter settings."	Market Reporting	"Gin & Tonic, Old Fashioned"												RetailScout scales to 1200 retailers	RS_RN_yes	"Conditioned Feature Backlog, Product Offering / Product Design, Reporting Data Preparation"		NEO-1211	In Progress		0	0	0
Feature	Migrate MediaMarkt and Saturn clients to NeoLite	At the moment MM and Saturn are delivered via STC.     The main challenge is that users that need access to both clients cannot not be granted with such permossion due to current system limitation.    current solution looks like this:    !image-2018-06-08-11-46-22-747.png!         Benefit:    reduce HW load    improve ops efficiency         Acceptance Criteria:    Media Markt and Saturn can be delivered via NEO Lite    the clients can access both Retailers in insight.     	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			RetailScout scales to 1200 retailers	RS_RN_yes	"Conditioned Feature Backlog, Product Subscription"		NEO-2134	Open		0	0	0
Initative	Enhancing RetailScout Content	This initiative will include following features:   * Fair Share report   * Running Report   * 3 Rolling Months   * Enhanced Highlighting   * etc.    i.e. extending the content of the RetailScout.	Market Reporting	"Old Fashioned, Gin & Tonic"						14. August 2018			24. September 2018							NEO-309	In Progress		0	0	0
Feature	 Fair Share	"Provide new module ""Fair Share""         Benefit:    improve customer satisfaction    Business Value:    5    Acceptance Criteria:   * Report is available on LP ( including tooltip)   * Calculation of new KPIs is done   * Sector, category, PGs and Brands, no items can be added in  Side Heading   * Provide new visualisation - first step left part, then right part   * Provide new tooltips to describe the figures on the chart   * Excel, PPT exports shall be supported   * Favorites and Collections shall be supported"	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Enhancing RetailScout Content	RS_RN_yes	"Conditioned Feature Backlog, Product Offering / Product Design, Unconditioned Feature Backlog"		NEO-274	Open		0	0	0
Feature	Replace full year by 3 rolling months	"Replace FY with 3 rolling month (incl. PYP).          Benefit:    1. significant value for the users, improve customer satisfaction    https://jira.gfk.com/browse/CCR-156    Clients have requested that a quarterly view be available within the tool. We would like to remove the current ""Full Year"" view, and replace it with ""Last 3 Months"" which would be effectively a rolling quarter.    This would be valid in all modules where we currently offer the Full Year view.    2. Removal of FY will reduce data volume, load time and HW costs:  | |Incl. FY|Ohne FY|Einsparung (ca.)|  |PG – Level|593 sec|480 sec|20%|  |Brand - Level|1562 sec|717 sec|54%|         Acceptance Criteria:    FY has been removed    3 rolling month (last 3 month) and PYP can be selected by the user in the insight.         PP is OoS (was exluded during PI Plannig)     "	Market Reporting	"Gin & Tonic, Old Fashioned"												Enhancing RetailScout Content	"R5(G&T), RS_RN_yes"	"Conditioned Feature Backlog, Key Dimension Spec / Reporting Repository, Product Offering / Product Design, Product Subscription, Reporting Data Preparation"		NEO-766	In Progress		0	0	0
Initative	Sustainable and Maintainable Software Solution		Market Reporting	"Old Fashioned, Gin & Tonic"	"MR BI Team Team, MR PS Team Team"	Fotini Gonatidi	MR PS Team Team: Sprint 5			14. August 2018			24. September 2018	16						NEO-310	In Progress		31	5	11
Feature	Implement Monitoring - follow up	this is a follow up Feature targeting to implement the solution which was investigated in G&T PI.         Benefit:    improve development efficiency         Acceptance Criteria:     	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Sustainable and Maintainable Software Solution	RS_RN_no	"BI Layer, Conditioned Feature Backlog, Key Dimension Spec / Reporting Repository, Product Offering / Product Design, Product Subscription, Reporting Data Confirmation, Reporting Data Preparation"		NEO-2278	Open		0	0	0
Epic	Implement Monitoring KPIs for KDS RR 	"In Sprint 10 of Gin&Tonic the members of the the KDS/RR team have identified KPIs, which have to be monitored in order to ensure  that all component-relevant systems are up and running.     Acceptance Criteria:   - Monitoring/Notification for KPIs X,Y, Z is implemented   - .... "	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Implement Monitoring - follow up		Key Dimension Spec / Reporting Repository		NEO-2591	Open		0	0	0
Story	Implement Monitoring KPIs for KDS/RR	As a member of the KDS/RR-team a monitoring system must provide information if key systems of KDS/RR are up and running or alarm immediately or not.     TBD with architect - which monitoring framework has to be used.   monitoring KPIs are depend on analysis-US NEO-1849  	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Implement Monitoring KPIs for KDS RR 		Key Dimension Spec / Reporting Repository		NEO-2592	Open		0	0	0
Feature	Clean up AS clusters to enable efficient data storage	"Currently available estimation implies that the capacity of 1 cluster with 5 nodes is sufficient for 50 clients.    at the moment we have ca. 110 clients with at least one shipped delivery and have to set up a 4th cluster.     In general we have comitted to have max. 3 deliveries per client. This means all old deliveries (e.g. from 2017, or derlivered by ST-C) has to be deleted.    Unshipped Deliveries has to be deleted as well.         Potential Benefit:    * reducing HW costs    Acceptance Criteria:   * double check capacity of the 1 cluster / 5 nodes - it could be possible that the estimation is not valid anymore.    * evaluate and document the todos to clean up the clusters   * conduct the clean up, impelent automatic process.        * removed from scope: automatic deletion process is in place (incl. test coverage)"	Market Reporting	"Gin & Tonic, Old Fashioned"												Sustainable and Maintainable Software Solution	RS_RN_no	"Conditioned Feature Backlog, Product Offering / Product Design, Product Subscription"		NEO-1164	In Progress		0	0	0
Feature	Evaluate and document KPIs needed to be monitored	the goal is to evaluate and to define per sub-domain (component) which KPIs / Checks need to be conducted.    oos: implementation         Acceptance Criteria:   * per component team: discuss and document which checks are   * think about possible solutions and document them   * double check with architects and other teams	Market Reporting	"Gin & Tonic, Old Fashioned"	MR BI Team Team					14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Sustainable and Maintainable Software Solution	RS_RN_no	"BI Layer, Conditioned Feature Backlog, Key Dimension Spec / Reporting Repository, Product Offering / Product Design, Product Subscription, Reporting Data Confirmation, Reporting Data Preparation"		NEO-843	In Progress		0	0	0
Epic	Implement Monitoring for BI	This epic is to introduce the monitoring to avoid manual effort we are spending there and also to get some metrics on performance and so on..     All the details about the KPI's and the solution approach will be documented under the confluence page     https://confluence.gfk.com/display/S2/BI%3A+Monitoring	Market Reporting	"Gin & Tonic, Old Fashioned"	MR BI Team Team											Evaluate and document KPIs needed to be monitored		BI Layer		NEO-370	In Progress		0	0	0
Epic	Evaluate Monitoring for BI	"Currently there is no monitoring in place for the BI components. Often the issues are solved after they raise. Through monitoring we can better maintain the components and also evaluate the resources utilization.    As part of this epic we would like to    * Gather the KPI's that needs to be monitored for all BI components   * Source of information for these KPI's   * Missing log/source of information for any of the KPI's   * Possible solutions to implement a centralized dashboard   * Align and discuss with architects to have a common approach for whole NEO    *Some examples:*    *KPI's:*   * JEE Status per comptype/DataMart   * Job Monitoring   * JEEJobTools (Monitoring, Analysing, reenqueue   * Queue length   * Waiting time   * Jobs processed per hour/day    *Server/Machine:*   * CPU load   * Memory usage    *Availability:*   * **Applications in different environments up and running    * Response time for the URL..    Findings would be updated at [https://confluence.gfk.com/display/S2/Monitoring+KPI%27s+for+BI+Components]"	Market Reporting	"Gin & Tonic, Old Fashioned"						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Evaluate and document KPIs needed to be monitored		BI Layer		NEO-1657	In Progress		0	0	0
Feature	Optimize BI Node Configuration	"As the Market Reporting team we want to optimize the BI Node configuration to save costs, reduce the amount of configurations, reduce the overall export/report execution time and support a effective untilization of datamarts.    *Business Value*: 2    *Acceptance Criteria*   * overall export/report execution time improved significantly   * overall export/report execution time improvment documented and communicated   * cost savings realized, documented and communciated   * effective utilization of datamarts documented, proved and communciated   * amount of configuration reduced, documented and communciated   * BI subsystem tested end-to-end"	Market Reporting	"Old Fashioned, Gin & Tonic"						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Sustainable and Maintainable Software Solution	RS_RN_no	"BI Layer, Conditioned Feature Backlog"		NEO-2448	In Progress		0	0	0
Epic	Increase the Number parallel exports on a BI Node to maximize the datamart utilization	"Currently to handle exports use case each BI Node is set up with 8 exports slots(8 App server instances), 4 DB connections and 8 DOP.    The number of export slots have to be increased on the BI machines to utilize the datamarts efficiently. The export slots should be in proportion to the size of the datamart."	Market Reporting	"Gin & Tonic, Old Fashioned"						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Optimize BI Node Configuration		BI Layer		NEO-2405	In Progress		0	0	0
Epic	BI Node to use multiple export slots instead of multiple app server instances	Through this epic we would like evaluate case 4 of the BI Node set up mentioned in the confluence page [https://confluence.gfk.com/display/S2/01.+Possible+Solutions+-+BI+Nodes+Move+to+Platinum+Cloud.]    If the evaluation in the POC machine works fine then we have to change the set up in all the environments that are created in the platinum cloud. Below    * CPU usage of datamarts   * Memory usage on the BI Node VM's set up in platinum cloud    Accordingly we should modify our automated config tool and deployment tool to support this new configuration.	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Optimize BI Node Configuration		BI Layer		NEO-1525	Open		0	0	0
Feature	Evaluation Meta Data Model Decoupling from StarTrack	"As the Market Reporitng team, we want decouple our needed meta data from the StarTrack system to be independent from StarTrack releases, changes and resources. For this reason we want to evaluate what is possible and what is needed to do this decoupling step.    *acceptance criteria*   * all relevant meta data model dependencies to StarTrack checked and documented   * possible solutions analysed and documented   * decision for one alternative was taken and documented   * further features to implement this decision discussed with the team and the technical lead   * feature for implementation added to the backlog     "	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Sustainable and Maintainable Software Solution	RS_RN_no	"BI Layer, Conditioned Feature Backlog, Key Dimension Spec / Reporting Repository, Reporting Data Preparation"		NEO-288	Open		0	0	0
Feature	Job Execution Environment (JEE) Infrastructure Decoupling from StarTrack	"As the BI team, we want decouple our Job Execution Environment (JEE) from the StarTrack system infrastructure so that we are independend from StarTrack releases, changes, resources. Additionally we want to check if we can replace the self developed solution JEE by a standard job execution solution.    *Acceptance Criteria   * Anyalse alternative solutions   * If JEE remains   ** Market Reporting JEE infrastructure provided   ** Market Reporting JEE infrastructure configured   ** Market Reporting JEE infrastructure tested   ** Market Reporting JEE infrastructure up and running   *  Otherwise   ** Standard system configured, tested, up and running"	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Sustainable and Maintainable Software Solution	RS_RN_no	"BI Layer, Conditioned Feature Backlog"		NEO-1554	Open		0	0	0
Feature	Replace MDM master data load by DWH master data load	As the Reporting Repository team we want to replace our existing MDM master data load solution by a more sustainable one and load all master data from the StarTrack DWH schema. Reason for that is to get the more consistent data which are available in StarTrack DWH and get rid of StarTrack internal dependencies and inconsistencies between the MDM and the DWH.    *Acceptance Criteria*   * all MDM date are replaced by the DWH data   * all data will be loaded via an DWH interface (standard database interface)   * no MDM interface will be used anymore   * the data load pipeline is tested and documented    *Business Value*    4	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Sustainable and Maintainable Software Solution	RS_RN_no	"Conditioned Feature Backlog, Key Dimension Spec / Reporting Repository, StarTrack"		NEO-2593	Open		0	0	0
Feature	Reporting Repository API is downward compatible	As the Reporting Repository team we want to offer downward compatible APIs.    *Acceptance Criteria*   * all API versions are fully downward compatible   * API are tested and tests passed   * API documentation adjusted    *Value*   * better maintainablility and better usage of the APIs   * cost reductions by the improved maintainability    *Business Value*    3     	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Sustainable and Maintainable Software Solution	RS_RN_no	"Conditioned Feature Backlog, Key Dimension Spec / Reporting Repository"		NEO-2541	Open		0	0	0
Epic	Reporting Repository API is downward compatible		Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Reporting Repository API is downward compatible	API	Key Dimension Spec / Reporting Repository		NEO-2576	Open		0	0	0
Story	RR: Standardize Version 2 RR API to include existing Version 1 API	"As an API consumer from RDC Team, I would like the RR Version 2 (V2) API to also include the existing Version 1 (V1) API so that RDC project will only need to use the V2 API and not both V1 and V2.    Acceptance Criteria:   * Standardize RR V2 API to include below API that exists in V1 previously with some minor changes:   ** /v1/hierarchy/dimension   ** /v1/hierarchies/\{dimensionId}/\{referenceSystemId}   *** to decide whether \{referenceSystemId} is still needed because it is always refer to ""Reporting Repository"" currently with Id: 11.   ** /v1/hierarchies/\{dimensionId}/\{referenceSystemId}/\{referenceId}   *** to decide whether \{referenceSystemId} is still needed because it is always refer to ""Reporting Repository"" currently with Id: 11.   ** /v1/hierarchies/\{hierarchyId}/contexts   *** context should no longer be used in v2; use \{hierarchyVersionId} instead."	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Reporting Repository API is downward compatible		Key Dimension Spec / Reporting Repository		NEO-2224	Open		0	0	0
Feature	Replace Aerospike client copy in QueryService with library import	"As the offering team we want to replace the copied and GfK specific adjusted AeroSpike client by the standard AeroSpike library. Furthermore we want (and we really want to) to use the most recent AerospikeClient version.    *Acceptance Criteria*   * Functionality that was previously added to the AerospikeClient sourcecode is still provided by the service.    * The QueryService no longer contains a copy of the AerospikeClient sourcecode, but uses a library import instead.    * The AerospikeServer has a version supporting the imported AerospikeClient version."	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Sustainable and Maintainable Software Solution	RS_RN_no	"Conditioned Feature Backlog, Product Offering / Product Design"		NEO-2340	Open		0	0	0
Epic	Replace Aerospike sourcecode in QueryService with library import	Replace inserted old library code with library in the QueryService.	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Replace Aerospike client copy in QueryService with library import		Product Offering / Product Design		NEO-2341	Open		0	0	0
Story	Replace Aerospike sourcecode in QueryService with library import	"The QueryServices currently uses a copy of the AerospikeClient sourcecode from Oktober 2015.    In proper form, it would instead simply import the AerospikeClient library as dependancy via gradle.    Changing this is not trivial, since the sourcecode contains manual changed and minor additional functions, that first need to be refactored out of the AerospikeClient and into the service, before the AerospikeClient sourcecode can be removed in favor of a library import.      Furthermore, if we want (and we really want to) to use the most recent AerospikeClient version, {color:red}*this may make it necessary to update the used version of our AerospikeServers as well*{color}."	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Replace Aerospike sourcecode in QueryService with library import		Product Offering / Product Design		NEO-2332	Open		0	0	0
Feature	Upgrade WildFly 12	"Currently we use WildFly 10.1 which is quite outdated    Benefit:   * Potential improvements can help reducing complexity and machine provisioning effort (e.g WildFly may replace Apache SSL certificate termination)   * compliant with technology map    Major Effort on DevOps side:   * there will be effort to change Puppet scripts   * approx. 4 servers need to be adjusted per non-prod environment, 8 server for prod    Out of scope of this meeting are:   * replacement of Apache server   * replacement of Tomcat servers   * replacement of Tomcat security plugin    more information, please see:    https://confluence.gfk.com/display/S2/2018-03-28+WildFly+12+Upgrade"	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned	"MR BI Team Team, MR PS Team Team"	Fotini Gonatidi	MR PS Team Team: Sprint 5			14. August 2018			24. September 2018	16		Sustainable and Maintainable Software Solution	RS_RN_no	"BI Layer, Conditioned Feature Backlog, Key Dimension Spec / Reporting Repository, Product Offering / Product Design, Product Subscription, Reporting Data Confirmation, Reporting Data Preparation"		NEO-1210	In Progress		31	5	11
Epic	PO: Upgrade WildFly on ExternalServices		Market Reporting	Old Fashioned	MR PS Team Team		MR PS Team Team: Sprint 5			11. September 2018			24. September 2018	8		Upgrade WildFly 12	RS_RN_no	Product Offering / Product Design		NEO-1765	Open		0	0	8
Story	Upgrade ExternalServices to WildFly 12 	h1. Description    The ExternalServices need to be updated to WildFly 12	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned	MR PS Team Team		MR PS Team Team: Sprint 5			11. September 2018			24. September 2018	8		PO: Upgrade WildFly on ExternalServices		Product Offering / Product Design		NEO-1974	Open		0	0	8
Epic	WildFly 12 Upgrade for BI	"We have to upgrade to WildFly in version 12. Details related to the upgrade are below    https://confluence.gfk.com/display/S2/2018-03-28+WildFly+12+Upgrade     Following are the steps / tasks for the upgrade:    * Update / Customization puppet script to roll out a WildFly 12 system (DevOps Team)  * Test if CLI based Deploy script with WildFly 12 still works (Build Mgmt. Team)  * (opt.) test if CLI deployment without server restart process can be resumed in the deploy process (Build Mgmt. Team)  * Update / modification of the installer script to customize the local development environment (Build Mgmt. Team + CL Team as consumer)  * Raising all previous Java EE applications running on WildFly version 10.1 to run on WildFly 12 through local testing (all domain teams)  * Gradual roll out of the upgrade to DEV, TEST, MAINT, DEMO, PROD environment via puppet runs (DevOps Team)  "	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned	"MR BI Team Team, MR PS Team Team"	Fotini Gonatidi	MR PS Team Team: Sprint 5			14. August 2018			24. September 2018	8		Upgrade WildFly 12		BI Layer		NEO-1139	Open		63	5	3
Story	Update ST2 installer to have wildfly 12 in local machines and test the upgrade	As part of this story we have to update the ST2 installer so that we can receive an update to wildfly 12 on our local machines.    Once the wildfly is upgraded we have to test if the all the below services are working as before   * Export Services   * Project Services   * Load Status Services   * Datamart Configuration Services	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned										5		WildFly 12 Upgrade for BI		BI Layer		NEO-2049	Closed		100	5	0
Story	BI | Roll out WildFly 12 into different environments	As part of this story we would like to rollout wildfly 12 to all the below environments:   * Dev   * Test   * Maintenance   * Production    And also check in the development environment if the CLI deployment scripts are still working with the upgraded version or if we have to change them.	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned	MR BI Team Team	Fotini Gonatidi				14. August 2018			24. September 2018	0		WildFly 12 Upgrade for BI	DevOps	BI Layer		NEO-2050	Open		0	0	0
Sub-Task	Upgrade to wildfly in the development environment		Market Reporting	Old Fashioned	MR BI Team Team	Fotini Gonatidi				14. August 2018			24. September 2018			BI | Roll out WildFly 12 into different environments		BI Layer		NEO-1805	Open		0	0	0
Sub-Task	Upgrade to wildfly 12 in the test environment		Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			BI | Roll out WildFly 12 into different environments		BI Layer		NEO-1806	Open		0	0	0
Sub-Task	Upgrade to wildfly 12 in the maintenance environment		Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			BI | Roll out WildFly 12 into different environments		BI Layer		NEO-1807	Open		0	0	0
Sub-Task	Upgrade to wildfly 12 in the production environment		Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			BI | Roll out WildFly 12 into different environments		BI Layer		NEO-1808	Open		0	0	0
Story	To develop Ansible playbook to trigger the wildfly upgrade	As part of this story we would like to develop Ansible playbook so that we can trigger the wildfly upgrade. 	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned	MR PS Team Team		MR PS Team Team: Sprint 5			11. September 2018			24. September 2018	3		WildFly 12 Upgrade for BI		BI Layer		NEO-2285	Waiting / Blocked		0	0	3
Story	To analyze and understand how the scripts needs to be written in Ansible	Understand how the puppet scripts are working to upgrade the wildfly to form a base how the scripts needs to be written in Ansible     	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			WildFly 12 Upgrade for BI		BI Layer		NEO-2282	Waiting / Blocked		0	0	0
Epic	WildFly 12 Upgrade for RDC		Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Upgrade WildFly 12		Reporting Data Confirmation		NEO-2467	In Progress		0	0	0
Story	WildFly 12 Upgrade		Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			WildFly 12 Upgrade for RDC		Reporting Data Confirmation		NEO-2468	Ready for QA		0	0	0
Feature	BI CI/CD pipeline	"As the BI team we want to have a build deployment pipeline for our BI nodes (ApplicationServer, Agent, Listenr) in place.    *acceptance criteria   * build pipeline created and tested   * build process documented    *Remark: final build and deployment solution should be completely independent from StarTrack (e.g. Octupus)*    "	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Sustainable and Maintainable Software Solution	RS_RN_no	"BI Layer, Conditioned Feature Backlog"		NEO-1704	Open		0	0	0
Epic	Integrate StarTrack build with NEO deployment pipeline to Octopus	* Extend Jenkins with a job that allows triggering the Octopus deployment via the Octopus CLI → this allows to have single tool to be used for deployments.   * Extend the BI Layer aggregator and component deploy pipeline based on groovy scripts to individually deploy BI layer components to any environment from Jenkins → this allows alignment to general groovy based deployment process and to get rid of Octopus	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			BI CI/CD pipeline		BI Layer		NEO-1778	Open		0	0	0
Feature	Make Insight UI development more independent of the data supply 	As the Offering team we want to be more independent of the data supplier back-end so that we can also develop the InsightUI application if the Offering specific (e.g. AeroSpike) or any other back-end (e.g. PS) are not available.    *Acceptance criteria*   * Mocking data solution evaluated and analysed   * Solution implemented and tested   * Solution reviewed with the lead architect   * Solution documented	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Sustainable and Maintainable Software Solution	RS_RN_no	"Conditioned Feature Backlog, Product Offering / Product Design"		NEO-2342	Open		0	0	0
Feature	Security - Latest OS and application security patches are applied	"As the security department we want to have a Market Reporting solution that is comply with the security GfK standards and constraints. In detail we want to have the latest OS and application security patches are applied on the machines.    This feature is based on the following security measures priorization workshop [https://confluence.gfk.com/x/TYOnD].    *Acceptance Criteria: *   * all the latest OS and application security patches (IIS, Apache, SQL…) are applied and running"	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Sustainable and Maintainable Software Solution	RS_RN_no	"BI Layer, Conditioned Feature Backlog, Key Dimension Spec / Reporting Repository, Product Offering / Product Design, Product Subscription, Reporting Data Confirmation, Reporting Data Preparation"		NEO-1136	Open		0	0	0
Feature	Security - Evaluation if applications configured according to application specific secure configuration guidelines	"As the security department we want to have a Market Reporting solution that is comply with the security GfK standards and constraints. In detail we want to have that all applications are configured according to the GfK specific secure configuration guidelines. In a first step we want to understand the guidelines and check if our applications meet these guidelines.    This feature is based on the following security measures priorization workshop [https://confluence.gfk.com/x/TYOnD].    *Acceptance Criteria: *   * configuration guidelines understood   * applications checked against the guidelines   * needed work to meet the guidelines documented (feature, epic) and communicated"	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Sustainable and Maintainable Software Solution	RS_RN_no	"BI Layer, Conditioned Feature Backlog, Key Dimension Spec / Reporting Repository, Product Offering / Product Design, Product Subscription, Reporting Data Confirmation, Reporting Data Preparation"		NEO-2211	Open		0	0	0
Feature	Rename Reporting Repository context tables	As the Reporting Repository team we want to rename the exiting context tables to improve the understanding of the data model. The context tables store data that are needed for the versioning functionality of the repository and should therfore have names that reflects this function.    *Acceptance Criteria*   * tables renamed   * documentation adjusted   * subsystem fully tested and tests passed    *Business Value*    1	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Sustainable and Maintainable Software Solution	RS_RN_no	"Conditioned Feature Backlog, Key Dimension Spec / Reporting Repository"		NEO-2539	Open		0	0	0
Initative	Improve Operational Efficiency 	This initiative will include following topics:   * Definition of the Features and PCL in the Key Dimension Editor   * CDM Enhancements   * Provisioning of only reportable data (Confirmed Layer)   * Provisioning of client-specific hierarchies   * etc.    i.e. topics which will enable operation teams to work more efficient.	Market Reporting	"Old Fashioned, Gin & Tonic"	MR RDC Team Team					14. August 2018			24. September 2018							NEO-1322	Open		0	0	0
Feature	Provide Feature and Feature Values for KDS 	Enabler Feature    Load Feature and Feature Values in KDS    Objective 4: Provide Feature and Feature Value for KDS via API	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Improve Operational Efficiency 	RS_RN_no	Key Dimension Spec / Reporting Repository		NEO-2477	Open		0	0	0
Epic	"Make ""Feature Value"" available in RR "	"In order to develop KDS it is essential to have in addition to ""Feature""-Dimension the ""Feature Values""  available in RR. Different to former dimensions the Feature Value is taken over from DWH instead of the MDM-scheme.   The Feature-Values have to be tunneld from DWH. For this an API is needed. Only used Feature Values in KDS are made persistent in RR."	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Provide Feature and Feature Values for KDS 	"FeatureValue, KDS, RR"	Key Dimension Spec / Reporting Repository		NEO-1881	Open		0	0	0
Story	Synchronize Feature Values to RR / Provide API to KDS to access Feature Values from ST directly	"As an intern. PG responsible and user of KDS I want to select as well as define Feature Values for a Feature. In order to do this the KDS application must have the values accessible. As the number of data sets for Feature Values is huge a Service API, providing access to the corresponding DWH-tables, is needed. Only final selected Feature Values of a KDS instance are finally stored in the RR.     Non Funtctional Requirements: performance when loading Feature Values for selection in KDS UI   Due to large number of Feature Value records (e.g. X thds To be verified)  for numerical Feature Type, no Feature Value from ST must be selectable in KDS. "	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			"Make ""Feature Value"" available in RR "		Key Dimension Spec / Reporting Repository		NEO-1814	Open		0	0	0
Story	Provide API from RR to KDS to access Features & Feature Value data from Reporting Repository 	"Provide an API to KDS application where the API should returned Features and Feature Values data from Reporting Repository based on the Product Group and Country filters that KDS application provided.    *Acceptance Criteria: *    * The external API for Reporting Repository service already exists and it should work out of the box where system will return features and feature values based on the parameter as below            -> hierarchyVersionId    * Additional Query Parameters have to be added to the API to provide filters on Product Group and Country so that the correct set of features and feature values could be returned from Reporting Repository to the KDS application.            -> productGroupId - integer            -> countryId - a collection/array of country Id.    * The API should returned only Features and Feature Values that are available in the selected Product Group and Countries.             -> For example, if Product Group = PTV and Country = France and Germany;                  system should only returned Features and Feature Values that are available                  for these 2 countries.             -> For example, if Product Group = PTV and Country = International; system                  should only returned international Features and Feature Values."	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			"Make ""Feature Value"" available in RR "		Key Dimension Spec / Reporting Repository		NEO-1916	Open		0	0	0
Feature	Establish confirmed layer (excl. UI) to store the rules	"The goal is to remove current workaround and to establish confirmed layer to store currently available conf. layer rules (please find description attached).    following interactions need to be provided:   * request and load available countries and channels shall be created   * possibility to define and store the rules for all countries - {color:#ff0000}white list!{color}   * communicate white list rules   * communicate channels and total/online/offline availabilty per country to be used during the dist unit definition    UI will  not be provided in the first step.    the rules will be defined and stored manually by the developers.    Benefit:    is an enabler feature to support in future feature with UI.    Acceptance Criteria:   * Channels and countries are loaded (with internal IDs)   * rules for all countries as a white list are defined for all countries which are already rolled out   * ruels, channels and availability of the total/online/offline is communicated and is used during dist unit definition.   * only reportable channels and pos type can be used in dist unit definition (in country context!)     "	Market Reporting	"Gin & Tonic, Old Fashioned"	MR RDC Team Team											Improve Operational Efficiency 	RS_RN_no	"Conditioned Feature Backlog, Reporting Data Confirmation"		NEO-301	In Progress		0	0	0
Feature	Stretch Objective: Enable automatic weekly processing of the content changes	"At the moment NEO Lite DBs are being updated oncy a month automatically and each week manually, what is causing effort on developers side.    There is a need to automate this process, therefor we need to provide a locking mechanism, to stop all data exports(at the moment a manual is being conducted) and to trigger new exports with new information submitted by the users.    e.g. of the changes: Add / Change of Retailers, Countries, Product Hierarchies, Dist Unit definitions.          Benefit:   * reduce manual efforts   * increase dev efficiency         Acceptance Criteria:   * automatic process is triggered once a week   * all newly submitted changes are available in insight "	Market Reporting	"Gin & Tonic, Old Fashioned"												Improve Operational Efficiency 	RS_RN_yes	"BI Layer, Conditioned Feature Backlog, Product Subscription, Reporting Data Preparation"		NEO-1519	In Progress		0	0	0
Feature	Stretch Objective: Conduct technical preparation for KDS	"Scope limitation:    this is an enbler feature and will be done as preparation to establish KDS.   * set up project   * request and set up DB   * prepare widgets and controls to start UI development          ------     Currently we have a workaround in place, which enalbe definition of the PCL and feature in GSE using LOBs. In future we want to remove such dependency and provide a UI (application) which will enable such specifications.    Benefit:   * remove manual workaround   * enable savings    * improve dev efficiency    Acceptance Criteria:   * provide a automatical proposal for PCL ranges in local currency per country, per PG(Base PGS? RPG?)   * provide a possibility for the user to modify proposal (incl. use of )   * provide a possibility to define 4 key features and belonging feature values    * for numerical features support ranges, single values or GroupValues   * for non-numerical features support single values and GroupValues   * check if each PG has a PCL defined (PCL definition is mandatory, featue and feature values definition is in general optional)   * reflect the PCL and 4 key feature definitions in the NL4RS     "	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Improve Operational Efficiency 	RS_RN_no	"Conditioned Feature Backlog, Key Dimension Spec / Reporting Repository, Reporting Data Preparation"		NEO-1950	Open		0	0	0
Epic	Enabler for KDS-Development	"Background :* Currently the definition of PCL and features is made in GSE by using LOBs. A LOB is created for each Reporting PG and country. In order to avoid this GSE-dependency and source of errors (due to one time definition without having an automated update process) a new application, called KDS will be developed. The full replacement requests the definition of a set of features for PS PG as a global standard and national exceptions, the definition of its corresponding Feature Values (auto proposal functionality) as well as PCLs for a PS PG on a national level/local currencies (auto proposal functionality).    The Feature NEO-283 will be broken down, based on the requirements placed by Stakeholders ([~aakais], [~iacris], [~Tristan.Irwin]) as following:   -> Define a set of feature for a PS PG as a global standard.  -> Define feature value for the global standard feature (auto proposal requested).   -> Define PCL for a PS PG for an intern. currency (global standard like Euro, US Dollar, British Pound)  -> Define country-specific set of features  -> Define country-specific feature values for country-specific feature.   -> Define country-specific PCL for PS PG (auto proposal requested).     To be done [~cnkrae]: add all the other identified epics.     A ""Global Standard"" can be copied and adapted to national needs (one or multiple country selection is possible).    This EPIC is the pre-condition for developing KDS functionality. Several technical preparations have to be done first.     Benefits : Decoupling of GSE. less errors in operations as well as updated source data due to automated synch process in case of data changes.    *Acceptance criteria : *  * Architecture Design - documented in Confluence  * Tech Design for KDS DB   * DB created in Oracle  * KDS-developing project created   * New URL for KDS are set up   * Extent RR Region Dimension by local currencies and Source ID.       Risk: : NA      "	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Stretch Objective: Conduct technical preparation for KDS		Key Dimension Spec / Reporting Repository		NEO-1782	Open		0	0	0
Story	SPIKE KDS DB Design 		Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Enabler for KDS-Development		Key Dimension Spec / Reporting Repository		NEO-1763	Open		0	0	0
Story	Design UI Widget and CSS for KDS Project 	"Before starting the implementation for KDS project, the UI widget and CSS for KDS have to be ready to ensure standardized UI being used across the application.    As a developer, I would like to prepare and design the KDS UI widget and CSS for KDS project as this is a new project and new user interface, which has a different look and feel from Reporting Repository.    Expected Result:  The KDS UI widget and css is available and check-in to the KDS project and ready to be used for development.  Error Handling    *Acceptance Criterion*  * (non-functional requirement) The design must correspond to the design of RR UI - new UI widgets are needed for KDS - however whenever possible - existing ones from RR must be used.   *  Based on the mockup of KDS project, design and create the UI widget and CSS and check-in to Master branch for future development usage.  "	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Enabler for KDS-Development	KDS	Key Dimension Spec / Reporting Repository		NEO-1833	Open		0	0	0
Story	Create KDS database in Oracle		Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Enabler for KDS-Development		Key Dimension Spec / Reporting Repository		NEO-1764	Open		0	0	0
Story	Create KDS Project 	"As a developer, I would like to create the KDS project with the necessary classes and library setup in the .NET project.  Pre-Condition  Spike for KDS has to be completed before the implementation of this user story: US-01: SPIKE: Architecture Design for new KDS Application    Acceptance Criteria:   * Create and setup the KDS project; classes, library, etc based on the technical design documented on confluence. (link to be added later)  * The service component should provides HTTP interface to all Reporting sub-domains as well as to the KDS web application.  * Create the GIT Repository / Jenkins project (the solution and deployment units) for KDS  * Aggregator  * CCR-Deploy-Config  * IIS Hosting  * ADFS Configuration"	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Enabler for KDS-Development		Key Dimension Spec / Reporting Repository		NEO-1766	Open		0	0	0
Story	Set-up new URL for KDS with ADFS		Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Enabler for KDS-Development		Key Dimension Spec / Reporting Repository		NEO-1767	Open		0	0	0
Epic	"Finalize ""Region"" Dimension in RR"	"For KDS property definition ""PCL"" the currency is needed.   Local currencies are an attribute of the ADM_COUNTRY table (see screenshot) - to be checked if Country-dimension from MDM contains this info as well).   !CurrencyInfo.png|thumbnail! "	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Stretch Objective: Conduct technical preparation for KDS		Key Dimension Spec / Reporting Repository		NEO-1884	Open		0	0	0
Story	"Complete dimension ""Region"" in RR "	As a MR (Sub)Domain I want to get all region-relevant data from RR.    AC:   * Source element IDs provided  * Country currencies are available (local currencies are an attribute of the ADM_COUNTRY table (see screenshot) - to be checked if Country-dimension from MDM contains this info as well).  !CurrencyInfo.png|thumbnail!      (relevant for PS and CL) 	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			"Finalize ""Region"" Dimension in RR"	"RDC, RR"	Key Dimension Spec / Reporting Repository		NEO-1770	Open		0	0	0
Feature	Communicate and apply CL rules	"the goal is to integrate confirmed layer with product subscription, Thereby commnucating the rules defined in RDC to PS and appling the rules by preprocessing component during data load into AS.         Benefit:    ensure quality and security    reduce manual effort on dev side         Business Value:    3         Acceptance Criteria:    Add the rules manually to the database (no UI)    Save rules manually (directly) to the database of the current countries.    PS shall use confirmed layer interface.    Confirmed layer shall provide NCDM the defined rules for the requested country.          "	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Improve Operational Efficiency 	RS_RN_no	"Product Subscription, Reporting Data Confirmation"		NEO-2460	Open		0	0	0
Feature	Enable Definition of CL rules via UI	"The goal is to provide a UI to enable operation team to define CL rules.         Benefit:    Ensure quality and security    hand over CL definition into Ops Teams hands, thereby reducing effort on dev side         Business Value:    4         Acceptance Criteria:    implement UI to define CL rules - as discussed and documented in mock ups.     "	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned						14. August 2018			24. September 2018			Improve Operational Efficiency 	RS_RN_yes	Reporting Data Confirmation		NEO-2461	Open		0	0	0
Epic	"RDP: Other Supporting Improvement/Tasks/Bugs for ""Old Fashioned"" Release "	These are Supporting Improvement/Tasks/Bugs current Release being done by RDP Team. These may not be directly related to any feature/Epics but are necessary to do it.   	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned	"MR BI Team Team, MR PS Team Team"	Fotini Gonatidi	"MR PS Team Team: Sprint 3, MR BI Team Team: Sprint 3"			14. August 2018			27. August 2018	6				Reporting Data Preparation		NEO-2588	Open		0	0	6
Story	RDP : setup/prepare  additional  server/DM's [DCEW-APRTPEN15 ]	As a DevOp i need the DataMart server be configured equal to the Production DataMarts     * setup DCEW-APRTPEN15 server/DM    +Dependency:+   * Database Users have to be added by GroupIT DBA         +Acceptance criteria:+   * User Add Sql Script is installed on Server   * RDP Team aproved that System is configured correct	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned	MR PS Team Team		MR PS Team Team: Sprint 3			14. August 2018			27. August 2018	3		"RDP: Other Supporting Improvement/Tasks/Bugs for ""Old Fashioned"" Release "		Reporting Data Preparation		NEO-2060	In Progress		0	0	3
Story	RDP : setup/prepare  additional  server/DM's [DCEW-APRTPEN14]	As a DevOp i need the DataMart server be configured equal to the Production DataMarts     * setup DCEW-APRTPEN14 server/DM    +Dependency:+   * Database Users have to be added by GroupIT DBA         +Acceptance criteria:+   * User Add Sql Script is installed on Server   * RDP Team aproved that System is configured correct	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned	MR BI Team Team	Fotini Gonatidi	MR BI Team Team: Sprint 3			14. August 2018			27. August 2018	3		"RDP: Other Supporting Improvement/Tasks/Bugs for ""Old Fashioned"" Release "		Reporting Data Preparation		NEO-2062	In Progress		0	0	3
Epic	Better CI/CD Process Longlist	This epics constrains some Technical user stories which RDP team feel should be implemented in order to facilitate the efficient development and deployment process which indirectly will help in stable/improved process/environments.     *+Value:+* :  Improved and efficient  RDP development and deployment platform/environments.        This has been prioritized for Old fashioned PI and needs to be aligned with PO's (Once all the User stories are groomed).  	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned	MR RDP Team  Team					14. August 2018			24. September 2018					Reporting Data Preparation		NEO-376	Open		0	0	0
Epic	Improve CI/CD Process for Old Fashioned	This epics constrains some Technical user stories which RDP team feel should be implemented in order to facilitate the efficient development and deployment process which indirectly will help in stable/improved process/environments.     *+Value:+* :  Improved and efficient  RDP development and deployment platform/environments. 	Market Reporting	Old Fashioned	MR RDP Team  Team													Reporting Data Preparation		NEO-2554	Open		0	0	0
